这些都是上周你你没看到的
This is what you missed last
week on Shameless. [Spits]
你妈还没怀孕
Is your mom not pregnant again?
每次她一用验孕棒  准保是坏消息
Every time she pees on
a stick, it's bad news.
然后我就崩溃了 一直想着我老公和我妈搞在一起
And then I get depressed
thinking about my husband
就因为我们想要
banging my mom 'cause we
selfishly want to have a baby
生出一个和我们俩都有关系的孩子
with some of our DNA.
大家注意了  Kevin要当爸爸了
Attention, people! Kevin
is gonna be a daddy!
为什么 你是说Mandy有点神经病了吗
Why, is Mandy going a little
cuckoo for cocoa puffs?
没错 我觉得 是她开车撞了Karen
Yeah, I think she ran
over Karen with her car.
- 我没有感觉  - 是Mandy干的
- I can't feel.
- Mandy did this?
就是因为我  你毁了Karen一辈子
Because of me, you ruined Karen's life!
我在你这么大的时候 我爸带我第一次抢劫
When I was your age, my pop
took me on my first heist.
我的同性恋养父们有挺多不错的玩意
My foster gays have a lot of nice stuff.
你有什么事吗
Whoa, can I help you?
我们有理由相信
We have reason to believe
this child may have robbed
这个孩子偷了他前任养父的东西
his former foster parents.
这些不是他干的 是我干的 把我拷上吧
He didn't do the heist. I did. Cuff me.
Mickey要娶的那个贱人
That whore that Mickey is marrying
就是一个在花园泉spa上班的婊子
is an actual whore that
works at Garden Springs spa.
你真的要和她结婚吗
You're not seriously going
through with this, are you?
我结婚了
Just 'cause I'm getting hitched
不代表我们就不能在一起了
doesn't mean we can't still bang.
我需要改变一下自己
I need a change.
我听说了点医学院的事
I hear reports of, um, medical school.
没错 我会在密西根多待一阵子
Yeah, I may have to spend
some more time in Michigan.
你说什么
What?
你已经申请要去上学了吗
Have you signed up for classes already?
按要求说 我已经通过入学了
Technically I'm enrolled.
你上次见到我女儿是社么时候
And when was the last
time you saw my daughter?
- 两天前  - 我是两个小时以前看到她的
- Uh, two days ago.
- I saw her three hours ago.
在移民局大厅
In I.N.S. holding.
这些都会解决的
It will be dealt with.
从你见到我的第一天
You have known from day one
你就应该知道
what you were getting into with me.
没错 是我搅进了你的生活
Right, I got sucked into your world.
我按你说的办事
I bent to your rules.
你让我觉得 可以相信你
You made me feel like
I could depend on you.
爷们一点 上船吧
Be a man. Get onto the boat.
嘿 是我 我爱你
Hey, it's me. I love you.
[High strung's the luck you got]
无耻之徒字幕组倾情奉献
♪ ♪
翻译  胡小贼  大姨妈
♪ think of all the luck you got ♪
翻译 小yy Yuhao  糯阿
♪ know that it's not for naught ♪
♪ you were beaming once before ♪
校对  爱小花的胡小贼
♪ but it's not like that anymore ♪
后制 大胖神
♪ what is this downside ♪
♪ that you speak of? ♪
♪ what is this feeling ♪
♪ you're so sure of? ♪
♪ ♪
♪ round up the friends you got ♪
♪ know that they're not for naught ♪
♪ you were willing once before ♪
♪ but it's not like that anymore ♪
♪ what is this downside ♪
♪ that you speak of? ♪
♪ what is this feeling ♪
无耻之徒字幕组倾情奉献
♪ you're so sure of? ♪
转过去
Turn around.
天啊  你又要把厕所炸了吗
Oh, Jesus. You hitting the crapper again?
不好意思 Frank
Sorry, Frank.
我一吃金枪鱼 就这样
Tuna casserole does it to me every time.
你就这么一个坏肚子的人
The bowels want what the bowels want.
我一会要和我的免费的律师建个面
I got a meeting with my free lawyer.
你那阵告诉我要和他说什么来着
What you told me to tell him again?
- Frank  - 怎么了
- Frank.
- What?
- 自我防卫  你是逼不得已的
- Public defender. Need a defense.
这个机会是上帝给你的 Julius
God gave you the race
card for a reason, Julius.
你就应该这样做
Play it.
你还好吗  你怎么不吃早饭呢
You okay? 'Cause you
didn't eat your breakfast.
我不饿 就是有点渴
Not hungry. Thirsty.
你看起来不太好
You don't look good.
到这个鬼地方以后 我就一滴酒都没喝过
I haven't had a drop of booze
since I got to this place.
我连个娘们都看不到
I can't even put my hands on a goddamn oxy.
这个地方以前还是比Walgreens那强多了
Place used to be better
stocked than Walgreen's.
- 这他妈的到底是怎么了 - 条子人手少了
- What the hell happened?
- Guards cracked down.
这一点也不人道
Well, it's inhumane,
就像糖尿病人不能打胰岛素一样
like keeping Insulin from a diabetic.
是因为什么呢
And for what?
一个完美的抢劫
A petty robbery.
那你    他们要怎么起诉你呢
And you... what did they get you for again?
用电话把我前妻打死了
Beat my ex-wife to death with a telephone.
- 有线的 还是没有线的   -  手机
- Cordless or landline?
- Sidekick.
嘿 你好像得看医生了 哥们
Look, it looks like you
need to see a doctor, man.
只要他们给我一点酒
I'll be good as new if these storm troopers
我就什么事都没有了
would slip me a malt beverage!
监狱的暴动 就是这么来的
This is how riots start.
Frank!
嘿 Carl 你别闹了
Hey! Carl, stop it!
你在他妈的干什么呢
What the hell are you doing?
用手把我的牙挤到一起
Trying to push my teeth together.
你能带牙套 我却不能 这事一点也不公平
It's not fair that you
have braces and I don't.
我比你大
I'm older than you.
你牙套上有东西
Ew, there's food in your braces.
- 你得刷刷牙了  - 刷牙干屁
- You're supposed to floss.
- Flossing's for fags.
别闹了
Quit it out!
蠢货 你在家拿水枪干什么
Jackass, what are you doing
with a water gun in the house?
因为我没有彩蛋枪可以用啊
'Cause I don't have a paintball gun.
那倒是没错
Actually, that kind of makes sense.
要是搬到密西根 我可得来把彩弹枪
Gonna need a paintball gun
when we move to Michigan.
没门
Uh, no.
彩弹枪也就最多
Hell survivors paintball
field is only 5 miles
能打5米而已
outside Ann Arbor.
- 我们不会去密西根的  - 不会吗
- We're not going to Michigan.
- We're not?
- Fiona说我们会去的   - 没错
- Fiona said we were.
- Yup.
那是Jimmy在这的时候  你最近看到他了吗
That's when Jimmy was here.
You seen him around lately?
就是这样
Exactly.
- 那是Fiona和Jimmy分了吗  -  我不知道
- Did Fiona and Jimmy break up?
- I don't know.
我每次一提这个事 Fiona就和我喊
Fiona barks at me every time I bring it up.
我就是因为觉得再也不会见到Becky Alexander了
But I picked a fight with Becky Alexander
才狠狠的揍了她一顿
because I thought I was never
gonna have to see her again.
- 看到谁了   -  上班就穿这个吗
- See who again?
- That a new look for work?
我要是在街角那上班  就穿这身
Maybe if I was working
the street corner, yeah.
可我现在在办公室上班 最好还是把衬衫穿上
But since I'm doing data
entry, I better put this on.
今天可是个大日子 Lip
Big day today, Lip.
- 随便吧   - 不 这可不是个普通的日子
- Yeah, whatever.
- No, it's not a "whatever."
你是Gallagher家第一个拿到文凭的人
First Gallagher kid getting his diploma.
- 这是大事  - 你是隔谁那买的
- It's a big deal.
- Who'd you buy it from?
他是正大光明的拿到文凭的
He's getting it fair and square and setting
他可是你俩的榜样  你俩学着点
a good example for both
of you, so pay attention.
我们得去参加什么SB典礼吗
We have to go to some stupid ceremony?
不 我就直接去教导处那拿到文凭
Nope, I'm picking up my diploma
然后就离开那个鬼地方
at the guidance office and
getting the hell out of there.
秋天没有典礼的
There's no ceremony in the fall.
春天的时候 他会和别人一起参加毕业典礼的
He'll walk with everyone in the spring.
- 他才不会呢  - 没错 他会
- No, he won't.
- Yes, he will.
我们会在那大声的喊 Lip   然后拥抱他
And we'll all be there to
yell, "Lip!" and embarrass him.
- 早安 - Ian 穿的很帅嘛
- Morning.
- Wow, Ian, looking sharp.
- 谢了   - 你要在圣诞节前一天
- Thanks.
- What, you got ROTC
去参加预备役军官训练营吗
on the last day before Christmas break?
没错 他们在办个什么冬季的训练典礼
Yeah, they're having some
sort of winter ceremony.
会见
Later.
你们赶紧把早餐吃完
Finish your breakfast, you guys.
别再说什么密西根的事了
No more talk of Michigan.
嘿 魔鬼女大兵  等会
Yo! G.I. Jane, slow down.
- 我可不想迟到
- I don't want to be late.
- Hey.
看到你好点 我很高兴
Glad to see you out of bed.
我还以为我们得全天看着你
Thought we were gonna have
to put you on a suicide watch,
省的你用鞋带或者床单上吊自杀呢
take away your shoelaces and bed sheets.
不要 我想明白了
No need. Moved on.
我得和你说多少次 我不会的 好吗
How many times you gotta hear no, right?
那就好
Yeah. Well, uh, I guess the good thing
我觉得你爱上Mickey Milkovich唯一的好处就是
about falling for Mickey Milkovich
你会发现 你会找到更好的人
is you know you can
always find someone better.
一会学校见
Aw. Catch up with you after school.
好的
Right.
Hey, Fiona.
你为什么还不去学校
Why aren't you getting ready for school?
我准备好了
I am ready.
我们今天就去半天
We only have a half day anyway.
一会要去Shelia家  Karen和Jody今天要搬走了
Gonna stop by Sheila's after.
Karen and Jody are moving today.
振龙是娘炮
Oh~~~~
你觉得
So you think Jimmy's
still gonna buy me braces
Jimmy去医学院上课 还会给我买牙套带吗
when he's done with med school?
不可能
Jimmy can't always be
我们什么事都让Jimmy帮我们解决的  Debbie
the answer to our problems, Debbie.
- 你们两个还好吗  - 你说什么
- Everything okay with you guys?
- What?
Lip说我们不会搬去密西根了
Lip said we're not moving to Michigan.
Lip把他自己的事管好就行了
Lip should mind his own business.
- 这关他的事 - 你说什么
- It is his business.
- What?
我们到底去不去密西根
To move to Michigan or not.
这关他的事   这关我们大家的事
It is his business.
It's all of our business.
- 赶紧去学校 现在  - 可你还没告诉我
- School. Now.
- But you didn't answer me.
我们到底去不去密西根
Are we or are we not moving to Michigan?
我不知道 好吗 我真的不知道
I don't know! Okay? I don't know!
我保证  我要是知道的话
And I promise that you're
gonna be the first person
会第一个告诉你的 行不
that I tell when I do know, okay?
大人的事 我们大人自己解决
Leave the adult problems to the adults.
我说那个人猥亵我
Oh, so it's fine for me to be an adult
帮大家抢回房子的时候
when it comes to saving this
family from losing this house
我就是大人了
by falsely accusing a
relative of molesting me.
可当我想知道
But when I want to know
我们明年到底住哪的时候
where we're gonna be
living for the next year,
我就是孩子了
then I'm just supposed to be a kid
你就要我闭嘴 是吗
and keep my mouth shut, right?
- 没错  - 那好 太棒了 谢了
- Yeah.
- Okay, great. Thanks.
♪ ♪
[Phone ringing]
我是Steve  留个信吧
It's Steve. Leave some words.
你玩真的吗
Seriously?
我告诉你 我想到解决的办法了
I leave you a message saying
that I want to work it out,
你就再也不给我打电话了 是吗
and you don't even call me back?
好的 我明白了
Okay, fine. I get it.
看来你压根也不想解决这个事
You obviously don't
feel the same way. Fine.
可你最少也得给我打个电话
But at least have the decency to tell me.
我们在一起两年了 我觉得你应该给我个解释
Okay? Two years? I think I deserve that.
祝你过得快乐 QNMLGB
Have a good life. Fucking asshole!
- 你不是Morgan Fairchild  - 你说什么
- You're not Morgan Fairchild.
- Excuse me?
这是天堂吗
Heaven.
我老是梦见苦艾酒和Morgan Fairchild  美国著名性感女星
I always imagined absinthe
and Morgan Fairchild.
我是Markman  你没死
I'm Dr. Markman, and you're not dead.
可你要是还喝酒的话  就快了
But you will be soon if
you don't stop drinking.
你有什么止疼药吗
You got anything for the pain?
凡可汀最好了  什么都行
Vicodin, Percocet, whatever's handy.
你肝脏受损严重 食管静脉曲张
You have liver damage, esophageal varices,
免疫系统失调  好像还有肾衰竭
immune system dysfunction,
likely renal failure.
说白了  告诉你没有什么病可能还好说点
Frankly, it would be faster to
tell you what you don't have.
可能你那网上医学院的文凭
Maybe the online medical school
还没到手呢
you graduated from didn't cover this
你就根本不知道怎么治这病
before they emailed you your diploma.
我想直白点告诉你
I'm going to try to make this simple.
事实上就是  你压根就不是什么医生
The technical term is "withdrawal."
我更喜欢  被轰走了 这么说
I like the word "parched."
所以 你要是没有
So if there's not a keg handy,
那一箱子的好药
a bottle of your finest pharmaceuticals
你压根就不能让我醒过来
should have me ship-shape in no time.
- 你不能再喝了 - 别和我说这些没用的
- You need to stop drinking.
- Spare me the sermon.
Juan会带你去办手续的
Juan will take you to processing.
- 办什么手续   - 你可以出狱了
- Processing?
- You're being released.
你说说呢么
What?
我们要是让你在这待着的话  我们就得给你治病
If we keep you here,
we'd have to treat you.
别喝了 再喝 你命就没了
Stop drinking before it kills you.
Aah! Fuck.
来一个  kate
Hit me, Kate.
我觉得可能就我能能让你满足了
Thought I was the only one here into that.
别再调戏我了 找个别人
No time for flirting, got
some catching up to do.
没谁了也
Line 'em up.
♪ ♪
- 早安 - 我想报名
- Morning.
- I want to enlist.
很高兴你来
Glad to hear it.
你是想全役还是预备役
Are you interested in
active duty or army reserve?
- 全役 专职  - 好的
- Active duty. Full-time.
- All right.
他们要是开始招特种兵的话
I'd be happy to help you find a specialty,
我会通知你的
let you know when they're classing up.
我不想等到特种兵那会
I don't want to wait for a specialty.
我想现在就走
I'm ready to leave now.
你为什么想要参军呢
Any reason why you're seeking out the army?
和家里闹翻了
Trouble at home?
犯事了 不想蹲监狱  还是把谁的肚子搞大了
Running away from jail
or a pregnant girlfriend?
这是我的成绩单
Here's my transcript.
我已经通过了职业资格考试
I already passed the
vocational aptitude battery
和体能测验
and physical exams.
下一辆去训练的车是什么时候
When's the next bus to
basic combat training?
明天早上
Tomorrow morning.
- 我还要带什么吗  - 带照片的身份证明
- What else do I need?
- Photo I.D.
到时候见
I'll be here.
嘿 你再好好想想
Hey, take some time to think on it.
我已经准备好了
I'm ready now.
那他知道我们要给他办个Party吗
So does he know we're
having a party for him?
不知道  这是个惊喜
Nope. It's a surprise.
男的一点也不在意这些屁事
Men don't give a shit about this stuff.
可这是个大事
Well, it's a big deal.
他可是Gallagher家第一个拿到文凭的
First Gallagher kid getting a diploma.
那你呢
Hey, what about you?
- 同等学历不算数  - 文凭压根就不算说呢么
- G.E.D. doesn't really count.
- Diplomas are overrated.
我什么文凭都没有 可看看我
I didn't get a diploma, and look at me.
嘿 都他妈的给我 Kev  模仿V
Hey,
don't give me no shit, Kev!
- 我声音可不是那样的
- I do not sound like that.
让我摸摸  你最好小心点
Oh! Give me those! You
better watch yourself.
Ow!
我要是这么弄你怎么样
How would you like it if I did that to you?
别咬我
Don't bite! No!
你还没他的信吗
So still haven't heard
from what's his name?
你能把那个横幅给我拿来一下吗
Do you want to give me
a hand with the banner?
我觉得 是时候我得去加点咖啡了
Oh, I guess that's my
cue to get more coffee.
他连当着我面和我分手的胆都没有
He didn't even have the
balls to dump me in person.
一开始  他就告诉你他是什么样的人了
He told you who he was from the beginning.
偷车贼 他用假名骗了你好几个月
Car thief. Lied about his name for months.
- 你这么想  - 不好意思
- Your point?
- Sorry.
不 是我的错
No. I'm sorry.
我不想这样的
I don't mean to be a bitch about it.
他是个胆小鬼 你就忘了他吧
He's a wuss, forget about him.
我已经忘了他了
He's forgotten.
就是觉得 我花了两年和他在一起 挺崩溃的
Just pissed I wasted two years of my life.
- 你们这么说不公平  - 你说什么
- You guys aren't being fair.
- What?
你上次见到Jimmy的时候
Did you or did you not tell
Jimmy the last time you saw him
- 你是不是告诉他 别回来了  - 那又怎么样
- not to come home?
- So?
他就是按照你说的做的  你还生他的气
Well, now you're mad at him
for doing exactly what you said?
她不是这个意思
She didn't mean it.
- 我是这个意思
- Yeah, I did.
- Aah!
可就是那个晚上 不是一直啊
Yeah, but just for that night, not forever.
我不觉得他会这么想
I didn't think he'd take it for real.
为什么不呢
Why not?
她就是生气才那么说的
Because that's what women
do in the heat of the moment.
- 我们这么说 不是那个意思啊  - 我明白
- We say shit we don't mean.
- I got it.
可他他妈的怎么知道 Fiona是这个意思啊
But how the fuck is he
supposed to know that?
去把车拿过吧 Kev
Just go get the car, Kev.
我们约的妇产科医生  要迟到了
We're gonna be late for the baby doctor.
好吧 可我怎么知道你是不是真的想让我去拿车呢
Okay, fine, but how do I know
you really mean go get the car?
你生气的时候 会说
You could be saying, "go get the car,"
去把车拿过来  Kev
in the heat of the moment.
一年中最崩溃的时候 这学期要结束了
Crazy time of year, end of semester.
我得告诉一堆成绩不达标的孩子
I have to let a litany
of underachievers know
他们最好别再想毕业的事了
they'd best be advised to cut their losses
学点不用脑的手艺
and learn a trade, something
that utilizes their backs
以后用得上
instead of their brains.
这个时候 才是我当老师最快乐的时候
It's moments like this
that make the job worth it.
我付出那么多  终于有回报了
Crap pay, miserable working conditions,
给一个孩子可以改变自己命运的机会
but the chance to change
one special kid's life.
祝贺你
Congratulations.
Wow.
我觉得的 我得   谢谢你
Guess this is where I'm
supposed to, uh, thank you
你没有放弃我
for never giving up on me.
- 好吧
- Well.
回见 垃圾
I'll see ya, Dick.
老师们在打赌你以后会怎么样 Gallagher
Teachers are taking bets
what's next for you, Gallagher.
上大学  10赔1  进监狱 4赔1
College, ten to one. Prison, four to one.
嘿 kate  能给我一杯吗
Hey, Kate, can I get a shot?
好让你逃课吗
And enable your truancy?
这个地方已经够糟心的了
This place is pathetic enough already.
我没逃学
I'm not skipping school.
事实是 他们让我毕业了
Surprisingly, they let me graduate.
太好了  这可算有个正经人了
Good for you. This one's on the house.
谢了
Thanks.
我知道你在想什么  你可以这么做
I know what you're
thinking. You can tap that.
可能你是对了 可你好好想想吧
And you'd be right. But chew on this.
没错 她是挺有手腕的
Sure, she's got some
frisky tricks up her sleeve,
可她可能更喜欢老屁股
but there's more tread on
those tires than it's worth.
相信我 上了她
Trust me, been there.
把我们家的旗插上
Planted my flag and I got
the piss pins and needles
好证明我们家后继有人
to prove it.
我还以为你在监狱呢  Frank
I thought you were in jail, Frank.
我自己有办法 出来了
Got out on a technicality.
你为什么带Carl去抢劫
Why did you take the rap for Carl?
因为我们是一家人  我应该这么做
Because that's what family does.
- 难道我什么也没教你吗  - 祝贺你了
- Have I taught you nothing?
- Congratulations.
- 谢了  - 祝贺你说呢么
- Thank you.
- Congra... what for?
你儿子拿到文凭了
Your kid got his diploma.
我的天啊
My boy!
你怎么没告诉我呢 我们得庆祝一下
Why didn't you say something?
We need to celebrate.
注意了 大家
Attention!
你们这群废物
Denizens of this dump!
- Frank 你还好吗  - 从没这么好过
- Frank, you okay?
- Better than ever!
因为我的娃 拿到自己的文凭了
Because my progeny has joined
the ranks of the graduated!
这也让那些当官的人知道知道
Which makes official
something we've long known,
我们Gallagher家的
which is that the Gallaghers
are head and shoulders above
比你们这些垃圾强多了
all of you shitbirds!
说实话 Frank 你就个是垃圾
Seriously, Frank, you look like crap.
你也一样  我说的就是你 Tommy
Even for you. You're one to talk, Tommy.
你才是他妈的那个
You're one bucket of kfc extra crispy away
为了一包KFC薯条谁付钱  就他妈的和人分手的主
from giving precious a run for her money.
Oh!
你知道 我有他妈的甲状腺病
You know I got a fucking
thyroid condition...
Oh.
我现在都能把你打得 你妈都认不出来
And I could still kick your ass.
那你为什么不把你钱拿出来
Well, why don't you put your money
把你那粪坑嘴堵上呢
where your halitosis-ridden mouth is.
嘿 我可不想再擦地板上的血什么的了
Hey, I'm not mopping up the
blood and the teeth again.
你俩看谁尿的远  把这屁事解决了
Figure out another way to
settle your pissing contest.
- 好 就看谁尿的远  - 没问题
- Fine, pissing contest!
- Fine!
开始吧
Let's go!
嘿 我就是说说而已
Hey, I didn't mean it literally!
那就伏地挺身
Pushups!
你连12个都做不了
You won't make double digits.
那有怎么样
What does it matter?
你压根就查不到那个数
You can't count that high anyway.
- 我也来   -  也算我一个
- Oh, I want in on this!
- Me too!
来吧  把这些桌子搬走
Let's do it! Push these tables aside.
- 等等  - 算我一个
- Hold on.
- Make a hole.
女的不能来 你也就会跪着俯卧撑吧
No girlie, on-your-knees push-ups.
就算有人跪着俯卧撑  Frank
Only one of us spends
time on their knees, Frank,
那人也不可能是我
and it ain't me.
- 好吧 我赌10刀
- Okay, 10 bucks in.
儿子拿着  我20
My kid will hold. 20!
谢了
Thank you.
谢了 谢了 好吧 购物劵不收
Thank you, thank you.
All right, no food stamps.
彩票可以
But lottery scratchers are accepted.
好吧  准备好了吗
Okay. All right, we're ready.
准备就绪
Get set!
开始
And go!
1  2
One, two,
3  4
three, four...
5  6  7
Five, six, seven...
8  9
- Eight, nine!
Tommy!
11, 12!
你知道怎么锻炼上半身的肌肉吗
Know what kind of upper body strength
扬帆就可以 Gallagher
it takes to handle a rig, Gallagher?
我能一天都做俯卧撑
I can do this all day.
这个不只需要力气 还需要耐力
Not just a test of strength but stamina.
耐力是成年累月积攒出来的
The kind one gets from
years of running from people,
不是你一天干18个小时 赶出来的
not sitting on your ass in
a truck for 18 hours a day.
27, 28, 29, 30,
31, 32! Uh-oh.
这些给你  你拿着去喝点吧
Um, there you go, uh, drink responsibly.
嘿 Kate 给我再来一杯
Hey, Kate, can I get another shot?
你想庆祝一下吗
Hey, wanna go celebrate?
- 吃顿牛排怎么样
- Uh...
- A steak.
- 算了吧 - 来吧
- No.
- Aw, come on!
你还有什么别的想法吗
You got something better to do?
去喝酒 来点龙虾吃吧
Make it a scotch and a lobster,
没问题
you got yourself a deal.
走吧
All right!
你好 我是Steve 有事请留言
It's Steve. Leave some words.
你是打算永远都不接电话了吗
So you just never pick up anymore, huh?
我是Fiona
Hi. It's Fiona.
你应该还记得我吧 Fiona Gallagher
Fiona Gallagher. Remember me?
跟你约过会的那个Fiona
We used to date.
咱俩应该还没分手吧
Maybe we still do.
我今天早上给你留了一通留言
I left you a message this morning.
没准你听完就删掉了
You should probably just delete that.
还记得我说过让你滚远点吗
You know that thing I said about not coming home?
我其实不是那个意思
I didn't mean it.
其实也是那个意思了 不过我只是指当天晚上而已
I mean, I did mean it. Just for that night though.
过了一夜 我的气也就消了呀 傻瓜
Not forever, silly.
对不起 是我自己没讲清楚啦
Sorry if I wasn't clear about that.
给我回电话好吗
Give me a call.
咱俩好好谈一谈
I'll talk to you later. Bye.
我准备了小袋装的坚果和蓝莓
Okay, so I've got little baggies
这些东西都可以拿来补脑的
of dried nuts and blueberries,which are good brain food.
太好了 妈
Great, mom, but I'm pretty sure
不过其实Sedona也有些这东西啦
they have all that stuff in Sedona.
可是那可是1642英里的观光路线呢
Yes, but it's 1,642 miles if you take scenic I-40.
再见了 Hymie 很高兴认识你
Bye, Hymie. It's been nice knowing you.
还有 记得找一个叫Shiva Ray的人
And you have to look up Shiva Ray.
我应该跟你讲过这个人
Remember I told you about him?
他是住在Sedona的一个医士
He's the medicine man that lives in Sedona.
我在网上看过介绍他的文章
I read about him online.
他只用小麦草 拿来给患者沐浴
He cured this woman's ovarian cancer
就治好了她的卵巢癌
by giving her wheatgrass douches.
－好的 我到了地方就去找她 －记住 是个男医士哦
- Great, I'll look her up. - Him. He's a him.
－他的名字叫Shiva Ray －好 我一定会去找他
- Shiva Ray. Him. - I'll look him up.
那我就放心了
Okay.
好了 全都准备妥当
All right. This is it.
我的天啊
Oh, my goodness.
我答应让你们走
I know I agreed to this, but it doesn't mean
可是我是真的舍不得你们
it's not hard to say good-bye
我的小宝贝
to my baby.
两个都是我的宝贝
Both my babies.
三个 三个宝贝
All three of my babies!
再见了 我的宝贝们
Bye, baby.
宝宝乖
Shh. Okay.
宝宝乖乖
It's okay, it's okay.
Karen 小甜心
My sweet Karen.
妈知道 终有一天
I knew this day would come,
要放你出去闯荡天涯
when I'd be saying a proper good-bye to you.
虽然这和我当初所想像的情景不同
It didn't really look like this though.
因为我没想到
You didn't...
你要坐着轮椅 还有 还有
you didn't have a wheelchair and... and...
你头上那么大的伤疤
a big... scar on your head.
妈知道是到了该放手的时候了
I know I have to let you go.
再见
Goodbye.
不不 不要告别
Just stop it. No more good-byes.
咱们马上就又能见面了
Just see you soon.
－马上见 －是的 马上见
- See you soon. - See you soon!
－马上见 －马上见
我的宝贝
Baby.
我们一安顿好就给您打电话
We'll call you when we get settled in.
我知道了 一定要治好我的宝贝啊
Okay. Go heal my baby.
我会的
I will.
再见 我的宝贝
Bye, baby.
再见 宝贝
再见 亲爱的
Bye, honey!
再见 再见喽
Bye! Bye!
妈爱你
Love you!
要不要我给你做点起司酪通心粉
Want me to make you some macaroni and cheese?
不用了 我得回去布置家里了
Uh, I have to finish getting the house ready
今天要帮Lip办个派对
for Lip's party.
那我去拿件外套吧 我也来帮忙
Let me grab my coat. I can come help.
好啊
Sure.
别担心
So don't worry, I'll make sure
我会帮你准备好一切的
that you have everything you need.
Lishman医生
Dr. Lishman?
嗨 Fiona
Fiona. Hi.
呃 我等会儿再过去找你们吧
Uh, I'll catch up with you guys later.
我很意外会在这里遇到你 你怎么了
I'm surprised to see you. Are you feeling okay?
没有 我只是想找您谈一谈
Yeah, I wanted to talk to you.
Ian还好吗
How's Ian?
他还不错
Fine.
不知道你最近有没有跟Jimmy见面
I was wondering if you'd seen Jimmy lately?
你是指最近吗
How long?
就这个礼拜吧
Almost a week.
你们俩怎么了
You two are having problems?
我们俩有点小摩擦
Things have been a little rough lately, yeah.
Jimmy就是这样 只要事情不随他的心意
Any sign of conflict or things not going his way,
他就会跑到一边躲起来
and he just... disappears.
玩失踪
Gone.
－你加辣吗 －什么
- Chipotle? - What?
我吃热狗一般都会加点墨西哥辣酱
I always have my hot dog with a little chipotle sauce.
－你也要点吗 －好的 谢谢
- You want some? - Yeah, sure. Thanks.
Rosa 两份特餐 加辣
Rosa, two specials. Chipotle.
他就是这样 我都已经习惯了
It's what he does. I've gotten used to it.
反正他一个月也不会打个电话或是写通E-mail给我
At least as used to it as a father can when his son
所以我也习以为常了
doesn't call or email for months at a time.
－给你 －谢谢
- Here you go. - Thank you.
没准这次他不会再玩消失了呢
Maybe this time's different?
是有这个可能啦
Absolutely.
这种事谁也不知道 不是吗
Yeah, you never know, right?
不好意思 我要回去工作了
I should get back to work.
别太担心啦
You'll be fine.
谢谢你请的热狗
Thanks for the hot dog.
好了 现在能看清了 只有核桃那么一点大
All right, there we go. There's the little peach pit.
我的妈呀 这就是吗
Holy crap, there he is!
看他长得跟你多像呀 宝贝
He looks just like you, baby.
就是啊 就是啊 是不是
He kind of does, doesn't he?
医生 现在能看出是男孩还是女孩吗
Can you tell if it's a boy or a girl, doc?
现在才12周 要再等一个月才能看得出来
12 weeks is too early to tell. Give it another month.
12周 你是不是算错了
12 weeks? That's impossible.
我们总共也才试了12周而已啊
But we only started trying 12 weeks ago.
那就说明你们第一次就中啦
Then it must have happened on the first go-around.
我把它打印出来 正好你可以把衣服穿起来
Let me print this up, and I'll let you get dressed.
咦 怎么感觉怪怪的
Ooh, yeah, that's weird.
按道理讲 我一怀孕马上就能感觉出来才对
My body usually tells me when I'm pregnant.
以前可没发生过这样的事情
You know, it's never been wrong before.
不知道这次是怎么了
Wonder what happened this time.
－你在干什么呢 －我要去预备役军官训练团报名
- What are you doing? - ROTC retreat.
－什么时候去 －就现在
- Since when? - Last minute.
－看到我的刀了吗 －什么刀
- Hey, where's my knife? - I don't know.
S.O.G军刀 Carl 我好不容易才弄到的
Carl, my S.O.G. Seal team. It's the best fixed blade I got.
我的武士刀坏了 修好之前 总得有把刀来防身吧
My samurai sword broke. Need a backup till it's fixed.
如果你不在的时候 活死人复苏怎么办
What if the zombie apocalypse goes down while you're gone?
谁来保护Debbie和Liam呀
Who's gonna protect Debbie and Liam?
－算了 给你吧 －真的吗
- Fine, keep it. - Really?
不过你要答应我 不能用在人的身上
Yeah, just promise you're not gonna use it on anything human.
－猫又不是人类 －只要是活的就不行 知道吗
- Cats aren't human. - Anything living. Promise.
知道了 那你可以教我怎么用吗
Promise. Can you teach me the different hand grips?
－当然可以 －太好了
- Sure. - Thanks.
－慢点啊 －怀了整整12个礼拜
- Hold on, now. - 12 weeks pregnant!
Veronica 你听我说 我真的不知道我自己怀孕了
Veronica, I promise. I swear I had no idea.
你们两个 等会儿
Ladies, please.
V 别这样 那可不对啊
Hey, V, come on, that's not right.
这一定要录下来才行
Although, hey, I should probably record this
到时候可以上传到咱俩的网站上赚点击率
in case we want to upload it to our site,
不过动手前记得要盯着她的肚子
make some money, just watch her belly if you're gonna hit her.
都已经12个礼拜了 Kev
12 weeks, Kev?
冷静一点好吗 宝贝
Just trying to keep the peace, baby.
宝贝 真的 我发誓我真的不知道
Honey, I promise, I didn't know!
算了吧 你自己心里有数
Please, you always know.
你自己就是根验孕棒
You're like a walking pee stick!
过去真的是这样 可是这次
Yeah, in the past, but this time...
别跟我说这次
There is no "this time."
你假装不知道 还不就是为了跟我老公多打几炮吗
You kept quiet 'cause you wanted to keep fucking my husband!
看什么看 有他妈什么好看的
What the fuck are you looking at, huh?
我他妈怀不上孩子
My husband fucked my mother to get pregnant.
所以我老公要跟我妈打炮 让她怀上我们的种
Sorry we can't all have our baby the normal way!
嘿 我要说什么才好呢
Hey, what can I say?
找个白种男人 从此你就紧致水嫩
Once you go white, you always stay tight.
不对 我这么说怎么好像是在羞辱我自己呢
Hey, I think I just insulted myself.
－妈 你就承认吧 －是 是
- Mom, admit it. - Okay.
我是觉得我自己可能怀上了
Okay, I thought I might be pregnant!
－我的老天爷呀 －但是 宝贝
- Oh, my God. - No, but, honey.
但是我不确定
Look, I didn't know.
我自己也没验孕
I didn't take a test or anything.
－因为我不想知道结果 －什么 为什么
- I didn't want to know. - What? Why?
因为我很喜欢现在这种状态
Because I liked what we had.
－谢谢 －你说什么
- Thank you. - Excuse me?
不是 不是咱们三个人的那种关系 我是指这种家的感觉
No, not what we, me and Kev had, what we all had.
－你到底在说些什么呀 －我最近真的好孤单呀
- What are you talking about? - Been feeling so lonely lately.
是你来找我帮忙
And when you called me to help out,
我才知道 原来我自己还有存在的价值
it made me feel wanted...
知道原来这个家还需要我
wanted in a loving way, in a family way,
重视我 爱着我
needed, important.
嘿 我是你们的小婴胎
Hey, I'm your baby fetus.
不要再吵了 好吗
Please don't fight anymore.
我知道Kev是多么的炙手可热
I know Kev is a big, hot stud,
他鸡巴那么大 是谁都不能拒绝这种诱惑
and you couldn't resist his giant cock penis.
但现在我才是最重要的人 好吗
But I'm all that matters now, right?
等了半天都没有人来给我续杯
What does it take to get a refill around here?
如果你穿得人模狗样 再系条领带 可能就容易多了
Jacket and tie would probably help.
这样真是太好了 我们太久没这样好好的相处了
This is nice. We don't spend enough time together.
我们压根就没好好相处过吧
No, we don't spend any time together.
没错 我就是这个意思
Exactly my point.
儿子 你知道吗 其实我一直都在这里
You know, son, you can always come to me.
谢谢了 老爸
Thanks, dad.
－我真的很担心你 －呵呵 是吗
- I worry about you. - Is that right?
不管你长到多大
A parent's plight never goes away,
在老爸的眼里 你始终是个孩子
no matter how old your kid gets.
看看你 都18岁了
Look at you, 18 now.
都已经高中毕业了
A high school graduate.
服务生到底他妈死哪儿去了
Where the fuck is that waiter?
又开始跟我打马虎眼了吗
Don't go getting misty-eyed on me now.
要不要老爸给你一些忠告
Need any words of fatherly advice?
－没关系 我自己来就好 －别这样啦
- No, I think I got it covered. - Oh, come on, come on!
你现在在想什么
What's on your mind?
随便了 反正今天已经够出奇的了
Okay, why not? Day couldn't get any weirder.
嗯 我决定不再继续上学了
Um, I'm done with school.
不过目前
I have no idea what I'm gonna do
我还没有任何的打算
today or tomorrow
以后的事就更没想过了
or for the rest of my life.
什么计划都没有吗
So no plans?
没有
No.
你好 我是Steve 有事请留言
It's Steve. Leave some words.
你是打算永远都不接电话了吗
So you just never pick up anymore, huh?
我是Fiona
Hi. It's Fiona.
你应该还记得我吧 Fiona Gallagher
Fiona Gallagher. Remember me?
跟你约过会的那个Fiona
We used to date.
咱俩应该还没分手吧
Maybe we still do.
我今天早上给你留了一通留言
I left you a message this morning.
没准你听完就删掉了
You should probably just delete that.
还记得我说过让你滚远点吗
You know that thing I said about not coming home?
我其实不是那个意思
I didn't mean it.
其实也是那个意思了 不过我只是指当天晚上而已
I mean, I did mean it. Just for that night though.
过了一夜 我的气也就消了呀 傻瓜
Not forever, silly.
对不起 是我自己没讲清楚啦
Sorry if I wasn't clear about that.
给我回电话好吗
Give me a call.
咱俩好好谈一谈
I'll talk to you later. Bye.
我准备了小袋装的坚果和蓝莓
Okay, so I've got little baggies
这些东西都可以拿来补脑的
of dried nuts and blueberries,which are good brain food.
太好了 妈
Great, mom, but I'm pretty sure
不过其实Sedona也有些这东西啦
they have all that stuff in Sedona.
可是那可是1642英里的观光路线呢
Yes, but it's 1,642 miles if you take scenic I-40.
再见了 Hymie 很高兴认识你
Bye, Hymie. It's been nice knowing you.
还有 记得找一个叫Shiva Ray的人
And you have to look up Shiva Ray.
我应该跟你讲过这个人
Remember I told you about him?
他是住在Sedona的一个医士
He's the medicine man that lives in Sedona.
我在网上看过介绍他的文章
I read about him online.
他只用小麦草 拿来给患者沐浴
He cured this woman's ovarian cancer
就治好了她的卵巢癌
by giving her wheatgrass douches.
－好的 我到了地方就去找她 －记住 是个男医士哦
- Great, I'll look her up. - Him. He's a him.
－他的名字叫Shiva Ray －好 我一定会去找他
- Shiva Ray. Him. - I'll look him up.
那我就放心了
Okay.
好了 全都准备妥当
All right. This is it.
我的天啊
Oh, my goodness.
我答应让你们走
I know I agreed to this, but it doesn't mean
可是我是真的舍不得你们
it's not hard to say good-bye
我的小宝贝
to my baby.
两个都是我的宝贝
Both my babies.
三个 三个宝贝
All three of my babies!
再见了 我的宝贝们
Bye, baby.
宝宝乖
Shh. Okay.
宝宝乖乖
It's okay, it's okay.
Karen 小甜心
My sweet Karen.
妈知道 终有一天
I knew this day would come,
要放你出去闯荡天涯
when I'd be saying a proper good-bye to you.
虽然这和我当初所想像的情景不同
It didn't really look like this though.
因为我没想到
You didn't...
你要坐着轮椅 还有 还有
you didn't have a wheelchair and... and...
你头上那么大的伤疤
a big... scar on your head.
妈知道是到了该放手的时候了
I know I have to let you go.
再见
Goodbye.
不不 不要告别
Just stop it. No more good-byes.
咱们马上就又能见面了
Just see you soon.
－马上见 －是的 马上见
- See you soon. - See you soon!
－马上见 －马上见
我的宝贝
Baby.
我们一安顿好就给您打电话
We'll call you when we get settled in.
我知道了 一定要治好我的宝贝啊
Okay. Go heal my baby.
我会的
I will.
再见 我的宝贝
Bye, baby.
再见 宝贝
再见 亲爱的
Bye, honey!
再见 再见喽
Bye! Bye!
妈爱你
Love you!
要不要我给你做点起司酪通心粉
Want me to make you some macaroni and cheese?
不用了 我得回去布置家里了
Uh, I have to finish getting the house ready
今天要帮Lip办个派对
for Lip's party.
那我去拿件外套吧 我也来帮忙
Let me grab my coat. I can come help.
好啊
Sure.
别担心
So don't worry, I'll make sure
我会帮你准备好一切的
that you have everything you need.
Lishman医生
Dr. Lishman?
嗨 Fiona
Fiona. Hi.
呃 我等会儿再过去找你们吧
Uh, I'll catch up with you guys later.
我很意外会在这里遇到你 你怎么了
I'm surprised to see you. Are you feeling okay?
没有 我只是想找您谈一谈
Yeah, I wanted to talk to you.
Ian还好吗
How's Ian?
他还不错
Fine.
不知道你最近有没有跟Jimmy见面
I was wondering if you'd seen Jimmy lately?
你是指最近吗
How long?
就这个礼拜吧
Almost a week.
你们俩怎么了
You two are having problems?
我们俩有点小摩擦
Things have been a little rough lately, yeah.
Jimmy就是这样 只要事情不随他的心意
Any sign of conflict or things not going his way,
他就会跑到一边躲起来
and he just... disappears.
玩失踪
Gone.
－你加辣吗 －什么
- Chipotle? - What?
我吃热狗一般都会加点墨西哥辣酱
I always have my hot dog with a little chipotle sauce.
－你也要点吗 －好的 谢谢
- You want some? - Yeah, sure. Thanks.
Rosa 两份特餐 加辣
Rosa, two specials. Chipotle.
他就是这样 我都已经习惯了
It's what he does. I've gotten used to it.
反正他一个月也不会打个电话或是写通E-mail给我
At least as used to it as a father can when his son
所以我也习以为常了
doesn't call or email for months at a time.
－给你 －谢谢
- Here you go. - Thank you.
没准这次他不会再玩消失了呢
Maybe this time's different?
是有这个可能啦
Absolutely.
这种事谁也不知道 不是吗
Yeah, you never know, right?
不好意思 我要回去工作了
I should get back to work.
别太担心啦
You'll be fine.
谢谢你请的热狗
Thanks for the hot dog.
好了 现在能看清了 只有核桃那么一点大
All right, there we go. There's the little peach pit.
我的妈呀 这就是吗
Holy crap, there he is!
看他长得跟你多像呀 宝贝
He looks just like you, baby.
就是啊 就是啊 是不是
He kind of does, doesn't he?
医生 现在能看出是男孩还是女孩吗
Can you tell if it's a boy or a girl, doc?
现在才12周 要再等一个月才能看得出来
12 weeks is too early to tell. Give it another month.
12周 你是不是算错了
12 weeks? That's impossible.
我们总共也才试了12周而已啊
But we only started trying 12 weeks ago.
那就说明你们第一次就中啦
Then it must have happened on the first go-around.
我把它打印出来 正好你可以把衣服穿起来
Let me print this up, and I'll let you get dressed.
咦 怎么感觉怪怪的
Ooh, yeah, that's weird.
按道理讲 我一怀孕马上就能感觉出来才对
My body usually tells me when I'm pregnant.
以前可没发生过这样的事情
You know, it's never been wrong before.
不知道这次是怎么了
Wonder what happened this time.
－你在干什么呢 －我要去预备役军官训练团报名
- What are you doing? - ROTC retreat.
－什么时候去 －就现在
- Since when? - Last minute.
－看到我的刀了吗 －什么刀
- Hey, where's my knife? - I don't know.
S.O.G军刀 Carl 我好不容易才弄到的
Carl, my S.O.G. Seal team. It's the best fixed blade I got.
我的武士刀坏了 修好之前 总得有把刀来防身吧
My samurai sword broke. Need a backup till it's fixed.
如果你不在的时候 活死人复苏怎么办
What if the zombie apocalypse goes down while you're gone?
谁来保护Debbie和Liam呀
Who's gonna protect Debbie and Liam?
－算了 给你吧 －真的吗
- Fine, keep it. - Really?
不过你要答应我 不能用在人的身上
Yeah, just promise you're not gonna use it on anything human.
－猫又不是人类 －只要是活的就不行 知道吗
- Cats aren't human. - Anything living. Promise.
知道了 那你可以教我怎么用吗
Promise. Can you teach me the different hand grips?
－当然可以 －太好了
- Sure. - Thanks.
－慢点啊 －怀了整整12个礼拜
- Hold on, now. - 12 weeks pregnant!
Veronica 你听我说 我真的不知道我自己怀孕了
Veronica, I promise. I swear I had no idea.
你们两个 等会儿
Ladies, please.
V 别这样 那可不对啊
Hey, V, come on, that's not right.
这一定要录下来才行
Although, hey, I should probably record this
到时候可以上传到咱俩的网站上赚点击率
in case we want to upload it to our site,
不过动手前记得要盯着她的肚子
make some money, just watch her belly if you're gonna hit her.
都已经12个礼拜了 Kev
12 weeks, Kev?
冷静一点好吗 宝贝
Just trying to keep the peace, baby.
宝贝 真的 我发誓我真的不知道
Honey, I promise, I didn't know!
算了吧 你自己心里有数
Please, you always know.
你自己就是根验孕棒
You're like a walking pee stick!
过去真的是这样 可是这次
Yeah, in the past, but this time...
别跟我说这次
There is no "this time."
你假装不知道 还不就是为了跟我老公多打几炮吗
You kept quiet 'cause you wanted to keep fucking my husband!
看什么看 有他妈什么好看的
What the fuck are you looking at, huh?
我他妈怀不上孩子
My husband fucked my mother to get pregnant.
所以我老公要跟我妈打炮 让她怀上我们的种
Sorry we can't all have our baby the normal way!
嘿 我要说什么才好呢
Hey, what can I say?
找个白种男人 从此你就紧致水嫩
Once you go white, you always stay tight.
不对 我这么说怎么好像是在羞辱我自己呢
Hey, I think I just insulted myself.
－妈 你就承认吧 －是 是
- Mom, admit it. - Okay.
我是觉得我自己可能怀上了
Okay, I thought I might be pregnant!
－我的老天爷呀 －但是 宝贝
- Oh, my God. - No, but, honey.
但是我不确定
Look, I didn't know.
我自己也没验孕
I didn't take a test or anything.
－因为我不想知道结果 －什么 为什么
- I didn't want to know. - What? Why?
因为我很喜欢现在这种状态
Because I liked what we had.
－谢谢 －你说什么
- Thank you. - Excuse me?
不是 不是咱们三个人的那种关系 我是指这种家的感觉
No, not what we, me and Kev had, what we all had.
－你到底在说些什么呀 －我最近真的好孤单呀
- What are you talking about? - Been feeling so lonely lately.
是你来找我帮忙
And when you called me to help out,
我才知道 原来我自己还有存在的价值
it made me feel wanted...
知道原来这个家还需要我
wanted in a loving way, in a family way,
重视我 爱着我
needed, important.
嘿 我是你们的小婴胎
Hey, I'm your baby fetus.
不要再吵了 好吗
Please don't fight anymore.
我知道Kev是多么的炙手可热
I know Kev is a big, hot stud,
他鸡巴那么大 是谁都不能拒绝这种诱惑
and you couldn't resist his giant cock penis.
但现在我才是最重要的人 好吗
But I'm all that matters now, right?
等了半天都没有人来给我续杯
What does it take to get a refill around here?
如果你穿得人模狗样 再系条领带 可能就容易多了
Jacket and tie would probably help.
这样真是太好了 我们太久没这样好好的相处了
This is nice. We don't spend enough time together.
我们压根就没好好相处过吧
No, we don't spend any time together.
没错 我就是这个意思
Exactly my point.
儿子 你知道吗 其实我一直都在这里
You know, son, you can always come to me.
谢谢了 老爸
Thanks, dad.
－我真的很担心你 －呵呵 是吗
- I worry about you. - Is that right?
不管你长到多大
A parent's plight never goes away,
在老爸的眼里 你始终是个孩子
no matter how old your kid gets.
看看你 都18岁了
Look at you, 18 now.
都已经高中毕业了
A high school graduate.
服务生到底他妈死哪儿去了
Where the fuck is that waiter?
又开始跟我打马虎眼了吗
Don't go getting misty-eyed on me now.
要不要老爸给你一些忠告
Need any words of fatherly advice?
－没关系 我自己来就好 －别这样啦
- No, I think I got it covered. - Oh, come on, come on!
你现在在想什么
What's on your mind?
随便了 反正今天已经够出奇的了
Okay, why not? Day couldn't get any weirder.
嗯 我决定不再继续上学了
Um, I'm done with school.
不过目前
I have no idea what I'm gonna do
我还没有任何的打算
today or tomorrow
以后的事就更没想过了
or for the rest of my life.
什么计划都没有吗
So no plans?
没有
No.
挺好的  你跟我真像
Good for you. You're just like me.
咱俩与众不同啊
We march to the beat of a different drummer.
每个人都想抓着你
Everyone will try to cage you in,
告诉你你得考虑自己的将来
tell you you have to worry about your future.
你知道你的将来应该是怎样的吗
You know what your future should be?
就像这样  充实活过每一天啊
This... living life to the fullest,
就像是你的最后一天那样
every day like it's your last.
只来这个地方实在是不够啊
This place is single-handedly lowering my tolerance.
咱们去卖酒的地吧
Let's hit the liquor store.
你真的觉得
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, um, you really think
他们这种服务也值得你花辛苦钱吗
they deserve your hard-earned money for that service?
-吃霸王餐  -吃了就跑
- Dine and dash? - Bite and bolt.
-吃了就跑  -我走前门
- Eat it and beat it? - I'll take the front door.
抱歉  朋友  洗手间在哪儿
Excuse me, amigo, uh, bano?
谢谢
Gracias.
抱歉 我一定要接这个电话
Excuse me, I gotta take this call.
- 我能看一下你们的甜品菜单吗  - 当然
- Can we see a dessert menu? - Of course.
Fiona  午饭的时候没见到你呢
Hey, Fiona, missed you at lunch.
这堆人在Mike的办公室外面做什么
What are all these people doing outside Mike's office?
- 应聘  - 非常感谢
- Job applicants. - Thanks so much, man, okay?
我们会在这周后期联系你
We'll talk to you later this week.
当然
You bet.
抱歉  我能跟你说点事吗
Hi. Uh, sorry. Can I talk to you for a second?
当然
Yeah, uh, sure.
- 有空缺的职位是吗  - 是啊
- There's a job opening up? - Yeah.
销售部的Rick要去哥伦比亚的办事处了
Rick from sales is moving to our Columbus office.
我想要这个工作
Well, I want it.
不行  我得找有经验的人
No, I need somebody with experience.
就是因为那天晚上在帐篷里的事
This is about our night in the tent.
- 我保证不是  - 可我已经在这干了好几个月了
- I can assure you it is not. - But I've been here for months.
我得临时工作快到期了  我也准备好了
My temp position's ending, and I'm ready.
我也很想让你继续在这工作
I would love to keep you around,
但是Matt大叔是不会让我雇佣一个
but Uncle Matt's not gonna let me hire someone
没有可靠业绩的人的
who doesn't have a proven track record.
但是门外这些人都有  好吗
Which all those people out there do, okay?
听着  如果你哪怕只有一次销售成功的经历
Listen, if you had one sale on the books,
这就大不相同了
this would be a different conversation.
我卖过鸡尾酒  这也算啊
I've pushed cocktails, that's sales.
等等  你不是要搬去密歇根吗
Wait, weren't you moving to Michigan?
你不是想要去我们安阿伯市办事处工作吗
I mean, you wanted to work in our Ann Arbor office.
而且我还说服了
And I convinced all those customers
你们以为快没戏的客户
you thought you lost to re-up.
你是提起了他们的兴趣  但是是销售部门的人
You got them on the hook, but it was the sales department
最后完成了交易
that closed the deals.
你对公司做出了很大贡献
You've been a great asset to this company.
我很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
我还记得我第一次带你来这儿的事
I remember the first time I brought you here.
去你的  你从来没带我滑过冰
Fuck you! You never took me skating.
我经常带你去滑冰  还有去公园  动物园
Always took you skating, to the park, to the zoo.
你还想偷乌龟来着
You tried to make off with a tortoise.
那是你
That was you.
那玩意在濒临灭绝物种市场里 行情好着呢
Huh. Good market in endangered species.
因为那是非法的  Frank
That's 'cause it's illegal, Frank.
- 心碎的环保纳粹啊
- Bleeding heart eco-fascist.
适者生存  这是有原因的
It's called survival of the fittest for a reason.
不想濒临灭绝的话  就给我快点进化
You don't want to be endangered, speed the fuck up!
- 长几根对生拇指吧
- Grow some opposable thumbs!
不然 你就只能变成eBay上值10刀的东西了
Otherwise you end up on eBay for 10 grand,
就像达尔文想的那样
as Darwin intended.
- 犀牛的话更贵  - 啥
- More for a rhino. - What?
它们的角  在亚洲的话足够支付一个国王的赎金了
Horn. Pay a king's ransom in Asia.
碾成粉末  有白痴说这能治好癌症
Grind it into powder. Morons say it cures cancer.
还有虎鞭
Also tiger dick.
他们吃了几口  就以为
They take a couple of bites, and they think it turns them
自己能变成性交机器了
into fuck machines.
我可不是瞎掰出来的
I'm not making this shit up!
我靠  这地真滑
Oh, shit! This is slippery. Whoo!
- 我得  靠  - 好吧
- I'm gonna... shit! - All right.
好了  走吧  走吧
Okay, here we go. Here we go.
- 我们应该经常这么干  - 午后酒友
- We should do this more often. - Afternoon drinking buddies?
我们明天能去动物园  偷出来
We could hit the zoo tomorrow. Steal it.
- 什么  - 犀牛角啊
- What? - The rhino horn.
一起去
Do it together.
- 你这废物  - 酒精能让我们保持清醒
- You're fucking wasted. - Alcohol provides clarity.
我们就躲在候鸟避难所里直到动物园关闭
We hide in the bird sanctuary until closing.
然后给犀牛下药
We drug the rhino.
它一倒下  马上用锯子把角锯下来
Once it's down, a quick back and forth with the saw.
然后我们就在拍卖网上点几下手指就好了
And we're a few clicks away from a bidding war.
你说啥
What do you say?
- 不不不不不
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
你可不是从男女同校的学校放春假的学生
You're not some co-ed on spring break.
Gallagher家的人不会吐的  快停下
Gallaghers do not puke! Oh, stop!
- 神啊
- Oh, God.
多米诺骨牌效应
Domino effect!
你们两个赶紧出去
You two are out of here right now!
- 他没事吧  - Frank  Frank
- He okay? - Frank? Frank!
Barry  快叫救护车
Barry, I need an ambulance.
有什么可以帮忙的吗
Can I help you?
伙计  难道你不知道在大街上
Dude, don't you know it's not cool
冲向独自一人的女人很不好吗
to rush a woman alone on the street?
他想给你这个
He wanted you to have this.
谁  这他妈的是谁
Who? What the hell is that?
和你一起住在这里的那个人
The man who lived here with you.
Jimmy?
等等  等等
Wait! Hey, wait!
他刚在在这儿吗  他现在在哪
Was he here? Where is he?
他还说了什么别的吗
Hey, did he say anything else?
有  他说他配不上你
Yes, he said you were too good for him.
他已经放下了  你也得这样
He has moved on. Now so must you.
拜托了  嘿
Come on! Hey!
Lip  怎么了
Lip, what's going on?
你好  我是Fiona Gallagher
Hi, I'm Fiona Gallagher.
我的父亲Frank Gallagher刚才入院了
My father Frank Gallagher was just admitted.
- 我查查  - 他怎么了
- Let me check. - What's wrong with him?
你是说这次吗 是我就不会担心 他可是Frank啊
You mean this time? I wouldn't worry, it's Frank.
- 我猜他得了癌症  - 除非得癌症给钱
- I bet he has cancer. - Only if there's money in it.
第一个路口左转  右手边第四间房
First left, fourth door on the right.
谢谢
Thanks.
在这等着  好吗
Stay here, okay?
- 什么  - 不
- What? - No.
等着  我知道了什么会马上告诉你们的
Yes, I'll tell you as soon as I know anything.
不要  我很讨厌你总把我当小孩儿对待
No, I'm sick of you treating me like a little baby.
- 我也是  - 好了  去大厅里等着
- Me too. - Okay. Go wait in the lobby.
现在就去
Now!
您好  请问您刚才是在我父亲的病房吗
Hey, uh, were you just in there with my father?
- Francis Gallagher  - 没错
- Francis Gallagher? - I was.
您能告诉我发生了什么事吗
Well, can you tell me what's going on?
我刚才都告诉他了  他倒是淡定地接受了
Just broke the news to him. Took it in stride.
可我觉得他其实还没明白是怎么回事
Although I don't think he's truly accepting it yet.
什么事实  淡定地接受了什么
What... what news? Took what in stride?
100美元之内
Under $100.
- 嗨  - 嘿  很高兴你能来
- Hi, there. - Hey! I'm glad you're here.
能帮我多要点这些布丁吗
Try to get me some more of these pudding cups, would you?
- 不  别提吃的  - 天啊  Lip  拜托了
- No! Don't mention food! - Oh, Jesus, Lip! Really?
你到底是喝了多少啊
It smells like a distillery in there.
我们去庆祝毕业了
Celebrating my graduation.
大白天的跟他出去喝得烂醉
Getting drunk in the middle of the day with him?
你是白痴吗
Are you an idiot?
拜托你等我明天头没那么痛了
Please save the mommy lecture for tomorrow, please,
再跟我来这套老妈谈话
when my head isn't pounding so much.
站起来  回家  清醒起来
Get up, get home. Get sober.
我们给你弄了个惊喜派对
We're planning a surprise party for you.
已经不是惊喜了  我早就知道了
It's not a surprise, I already knew.
Debbie和Carl在大厅里等着
Well, Debbie and Carl are waiting in the lobby.
带他俩回家
So take them with you.
这可不好玩
This isn't gonna be fun.
是啊  把你的惊喜冰激凌奶油蛋糕
Yeah, and grab your surprise ice cream cake
从冰箱里拿出来解冻
out of the freezer and start defrosting it.
- 好吧
- Okay.
三个生鸡蛋  伍斯特沙司  再加一片姜
Three raw eggs, worcestershire, and a sliver of ginger.
解酒最有用了
Works every time.
我的天  没有HBO  没有Showtime  只有普通的有线电视
Jesus. No HBO, no Showtime. Just basic cable.
Tosh 2.0是什么玩意儿
And what the hell is a Tosh 2.0?
- 医生跟你说过了是吗  Frank  - 是啊
- The doctor talk to you, Frank? - Yeah.
"叭叭叭叭叭叭  不能再喝酒
"Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, stop drinking.
叭叭叭叭叭叭"
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah."
他跟我说你真的病得很严重
He told me you were really sick.
你觉得我病得严重吗
Do I look really sick to you?
他说你吐血了
Said you were throwing up blood.
那是因为我有太多血在身体里了
That's 'cause I've got too much of it in me.
这是个过滤的过程
It's a filtration process.
我的身体知道该怎么样把脏东西排出来
My body knows how to flush itself out.
别开玩笑了  这很严重
Stop joking. This is serious.
他就是个江湖医生
It's just doctor mumbo jumbo
骗你去多做点检查而已
to scare you into taking more tests.
- 该死的寄生虫  - 你想干嘛
- Fucking parasites. - What are you doing?
- 我要去厕所  - 去找护士吧
- I gotta use the can. - Well, let's get the nurse.
我不喜欢现在值班的那个护士  她很胖
I don't like the one that's on duty. She's fat.
帮我推着那个好吗
Roll that thing behind me, will you?
他说你如果再喝酒的话 你就快死了
He said if you don't stop drinking, you're gonna die.
真的是死
As in dead, you know,
不再活着了  知道吗  而且很快会死
like, no longer living? And soon.
你什么时候开始关心我了
When did you start to care?
我不确定我关不关心
Not sure that I do.
我曾经梦想着你去死
I've dreamt about your death.
把钱放到募捐箱里的时候祈祷过
Put money in a collection box and prayed for it.
吹生日蜡烛的时候祈祷过
Blew out my birthday candles, wished for it.
如果这真的发生了的话
If it actually ever happened,
我不知道我是会感到解脱还是愧疚
I don't know if I'd feel relief or guilt.
你的生日蜡烛
Your birthday candles?
有一次我还给圣诞老人写信
I wrote a letter to Santa once.
所以我就不应该再喝酒了
So I'm supposed to stop drinking
这样 你就不会有愧疚感了
so that you don't feel guilty?
不是
No.
你不应该再继续喝酒
You're supposed to stop drinking because you have
因为家里还有爱着你的孩子们
children at home who love you.
我也不知道为什么他们爱你
And I don't know why.
如果你发生了什么事 他们会崩溃的
Who would be destroyed if anything happened to you.
坏事能让孩子们更坚强  Fiona
Tragedy makes kids tough, Fiona.
那就为了你自己这个大自恋狂
Then be the fabulous narcissist that you are,
你去戒酒吧
and do it for yourself.
如果我不想改变呢
What if I don't want to change?
那就是我一直最害怕的事情发生了
Then I would know what
I've always feared is true.
什么事
What is that?
就是你根本一点都不在乎我们
That you don't give a shit about any of us.
为了你自己
So do it for you.
为了你的孩子们
Do it for your kids.
那都无所谓
It doesn't matter.
你戒酒吧
Do it.
♪ yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
嘿 今天你去哪了 没见你去学校
Hey, where were you today?
I didn't see you at school.
有点事要处理
Something came up.
老师给我们圣诞假期留了作业
They gave us homework
over the Christmas break.
我告诉Stoltz老师 上帝可不想
I told Mrs. Stoltz that Jesus
didn't want us celebrating
用他妈的读书来庆祝他生日
his birthday by fucking reading.
你想拿你那份作业吗
You want the assignments?
- 我就是想过来看看你 - 谁他妈的敲门
- Just came by to see you.
- Who's at the goddamn door?
是找我的 混蛋
It's for me, shithead!
我弄了些硝石 给你拿过来
Got some nitrous. I'll go get it.
嘿
Hey.
这是第四套20磅了
Up to four sets of 20.
过来  给你看点东西
Get in here. I want to show you something.
来吧  过来看看这个
Come on. Come check it out.
我老婆让我把那些纳粹的东西都摘下来了
Wife made me take all my Nazi shit down.
她恨纳粹
She hates Nazis.
显然俄国佬们对待二战和德国人
Apparently the Russians
kicked some serious kraut ass
的态度挺严肃的 所以…
in world war II, so...
她能把我喝到桌子底下去 天呐
She can drink me under
the fucking table, man.
真稀奇
It's weird.
那个…
Anyways...
她明晚要工作
she's working tomorrow night.
要不我们还和以前一样
Why don't we pick up where we left off?
反正她也在外面干别的男人
Figure she's gonna be out fucking dudes.
为什么我不行
Why can't I?
不用了  谢谢
No, thanks.
嗯  越得不到的我越想要啊 Gallagher
Mm. Hard to get's getting
me hard, Gallagher.
我 嗯 要走了
I'm, uh, leaving town.
怎么 哪儿有什么同性恋集会么
There a queer rights rally somewhere?
参军
Army.
啊 是啊 不过你要满18
Ah! Right. You gotta be 18.
是 不过我能想办法处理一下
Yeah, I figured a way around that.
你说真的？ 你报名了？
You serious? You're signing up?
明早
Tomorrow morning.
这他妈的是件大事啊  去多久
That's a dumb-ass fucking move. How long?
四年 至少
Four years. Minimum.
你期望什么 我求你不要走？
What are you hoping, I tell you not to go?
我像个小姑娘一样的在后面追你？
I'm gonna chase after you like some bitch?
我来这不是为了见你的
Didn't come here for you.
别
Don't.
- 别什么？ - 别...
- Don't what?
- Just...
我拿到硝石了 外面见
I got the nitrous. Meet you outside.
好
Yeah.
你TM的想干什么
What the fuck do you want?
就这样  这就是你最想对他说的
Really? That's all you're gonna say to him?
你他妈的就是个娘们
You're a fucking pussy.
- 怎么了 - 哦 嘿 我刚喂完Liam
- What's going on?
- Oh, hey, I fed Liam.
半个小时前把他哄睡着了
And put him down a half an hour ago.
- 谢了 - 爸爸怎么样
- Thanks.
- How's daddy?
- 他还好么  - 那看他自己了
- Is he okay?
- That's up to him.
这是什么意思
What does that mean?
我们应该留在医院照顾他
We should be at the
hospital helping him out.
- 他需要自己帮自己  - 什么
- He needs to help himself.
- What?
你们怎么不装饰房间了
What's up with taking down the decorations?
Lip说不用的
Lip told us to.
没人有心思开派对了
No one feels much like a party.
嘿 有时候生活就是会把你绊倒
Hey, sometimes life throws
a couple swings at you.
但是我们是Gallagher 对吗
But we're Gallaghers, okay?
有两件事我们最擅长
And there's two things
that we're really good at...
知道怎么找支援和怎么开派对
knowing how to get back up
and knowing how to party.
所以你去把胶带拿过来 把条幅挂上
So you get the tape, start
hanging up that banner.
你去叫Kev和V
And you go get Kev and V.
Sheila 开始准备吃的
Sheila, start taking the food back out.
我去叫Lip 喔
I'll get Lip. Whoo!
饿了吗
Hungry?
- 不  - 热乎乎的鸡肉馅饼
- Don't.
- Chicken pot pie.
- 天啊 真的  - 茄汁三明治
- God, seriously.
- Sloppy Joes.
- 停 Fiona  - 这都是应该的
- Stop, Fiona.
- Serves you right.
来庆祝你毕业后开始崭新生活了
Hell of a way to start
life after graduation.
- 那东西在哪呢 - 什么
- Where is it?
- What?
那张纸
The piece of paper.
我当初都不敢确定你能得到这个
I wasn't actually sure you'd ever get this.
这代表了我们两个人的努力
That makes two of us.
我为你骄傲
I'm proud of you.
我今天拿到些钱
I came into some money.
你可以自己留下 你怎么不告诉我啊
Bury the lead, why don't you?
我用一些付了房租和水电
I put a bunch away for rent and gas,
但是剩下的我想做点别的
but there's something I
want to do with the rest.
拜托千万别告诉我你又要办什么夜店 晚会了
Please don't tell me you're gonna promote
上次都弄得我恶心了
another club night,
okay? I'm nauseous enough.
嗯 这次是别的事
Mm, something else.
没准可以弄个全职工作
Could get a full-time job out of it.
你说行就行 你能帮我把门关上么
If I say okay, will you
close the fucking door?
- 你得给我下楼去 - 我还晕呢 Fi
- You're wanted downstairs.
- I got the spins, Fi.
打起精神 然后笑一个
Get it together and put
a smile on your face.
Debbie和Carl需要点激励
Debbie and Carl need motivation.
快点 大家都在等着呢
Come on, everyone's waiting.
好的
Okay.
- 往前走  - 恩
- Walk forward.
- Mm-hmm.
好的
Okay.
然后
And...
惊喜
Surprise!
Sheila在这干嘛呢
What's Sheila doing here?
真棒 蟹饼啊
Yeah! It's crab cakes.
♪ ♪
你来教我们的孩子吧
You can educate our baby!
唔
Eh, well, um...
我要开始吃了
I'm going to go with ambrosia.
这些虾蟹饼真好吃 Sheila
The shrimp crab cakes
are delicious, Sheila.
哦
Oh.
我想明天我们可以
I was thinking about some fun things
一起做一些有趣的事情
we could do tomorrow together.
唔 事实上 Veronica准备带我去
Oh, um, actually,
Veronica was gonna take me
- 溜冰场  - 哦
- to the skating rink.
- Oh.
我很喜欢跟你一起出去玩 Sheila
I really enjoy hanging
out with you, Sheila,
但是现在你家里也没什么人了
but now that there's an empty nest,
也许你可以利用这次机会
maybe it's a good time for you
交一些跟你年龄相仿
to start making some new friends
兴趣相近的的朋友
closer to your own age
who share your interests.
也许
Maybe.
哇
Whoa!
恭喜了
Congratulations.
Debs 放音乐 一起来啊
Debs, play some music. Get it going!
嘿 Fi 好消息 V和我想出了一个
Hey, Fi, good news, V and I came up
折中的名字
with a compromise on a name.
如果是女孩就叫Amy 是男孩就叫D Shawndre
Amy if it's a girl,
D'Shawndre if it's a boy.
什么
What?
拜托告诉我这个是宝宝提前出场的礼物
Please tell me this is
an early baby shower gift.
明天早上 你得帮我
I need you to order a couple thousand cups
去给Alibi定1000个茶杯
for the Alibi first thing in the morning.
茶杯 这儿是酒吧 不是兄弟会
Cups? It's a bar, not a frat party.
我们用大杯子喝酒
We drink out of glasses and mugs.
这些你这从哪拿的
Where did you get this from?
告诉他们是我说服你的
Tell them I convinced you to do it.
好的
Okay.
怎么啦
What's going on?
厉害 治疗宿醉的最好办法
Nice. Best cure for a hangover.
真好
Sweet.
谢了
Thanks.
他这他妈的怎么了
Where the fuck's he going?
担心吗
Worried?
爸爸怎么了
What's gonna happen to daddy?
他会有办法的
He always finds a way.
我们不会搬去密歇根州的
We're not moving to Michigan.
我想让你第一个知道
I wanted you to be the first to know.
Jimmy走了 是吗
Jimmy's gone for good?
嗯
Mm-hmm.
可是 我可能会有一份新工作
But there's a chance I might get a new job.
- 在茶杯公司  - 也许
- At the cup company.
- Maybe.
那真好
That's great.
在事情确定下来之前别跟别人说 好吗
Don't tell anybody about
it unless it happens, okay?
还有福利呢
Comes with benefits.
牙医
Dental?
我也有吗
For me too?
别搞砸了 得到那份工作
Well, don't blow it. Get the job.
我试试
I'll try.
♪ Whoo, there's haunted
John, haunted John ♪
♪ ♪
♪ haunted John, haunted John ♪
怎么了
What's going on?
剃光头
Shaving your head.
什么
What?
让阳光照射进来 它们可以治好你的
To let the sunrays in,
so they can heal you,
就好象治好我的癌症一样
like they did with my cancer.
阳光 对的
Sunrays. Right.
用不了多久
Won't take long.
继续啊
Carry on.
嘿 小男人
Hey, little man.
我会寄明信片的 好吗
I'll send postcards, all right?
来了
Coming.
你好啊 嗨
Hello! Hi.
- 嗨  - 哦
- Hi.
- Oh!
Debbie, Sonia, Terry.
快进来 进来
Come in, come in.
- Gallagher吗  - 恩 谢了
- Gallagher?
- Yeah, thanks.
这些小根 或者说是大根
And this little gem... or
should I say, giant gem,
是刺激物 黑色子弹
is the black bullet stimulator.
他的表兄弟 是刺激物-银色子弹
And its cousin, the
silver bullet stimulator.
我建议你拿一些带回去
Now I recommend getting several of these
家里 车上或者旅行中都有可能用的到
for your home, car, and travel needs.
我有个杀手锏要给你看
I have one last item to show you.
这个是香草味的抗皱霜
This is the vanilla-scented
snug shrink cream.
现在谁需要填这些表格呢
Now, who needs help
filling out the order forms?
让我们来看看
Just see...
哦
Oh.
给你 真好
Um, here you go. Great.
用假名也可以 给你
Um, feel free to change the
name and... um, here you go.
还有笔
And pen.
♪ ♪
我告诉你的就是这个
This is the one I was telling you about.
这是Fiona Gallagher 做成Alibi酒吧的那笔交易的人
This is Fiona Gallagher,
made the Alibi Room sale.
很棒啊 本子上有记着
Good one. A sale in the books.
恩 熬夜 没少熬
Yeah. Overnight, no less.
给她两个礼拜的试验期 Mike
Let's give her a two-week trial, Mike.
- 看看效果如何  - 谢了
- See if it works out.
- Thank you, sir.
好的
Okay.
- 啊  - 耶
- Aah!
- Yay!
来吧
Here we go.
笔 纸还有办公室里所需的
Pens, paper, and all the office supplies
你需要的都在第一层抽屉里面
you need are in the top drawer.
你办公室的号码就在电话表上
Your direct phone number
is listed on the call sheet.
你要录个留言录音
You should record an outgoing message.
走啊 走啊 走啊
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Phillip
Phillip?
是Lip
It's Lip.
现在就叫Gallagher 上啊
It's just Gallagher now. Get on.
下一个
Next.
我们可以给你定一些名片
We can order your business cards.
哇噢
Whoohoo!
嗷 谢谢你
Ah, thank you!
你收拾好一下 Mike想让你和
Once you get settled, Mike
wants to have a meeting
其他的销售代表在今天下午见个面
with you and all the other
sales reps this afternoon.
恩 好的 谢了 Connie
Okay, cool. Thanks, Connie.
恭喜你了 Fiona 你让我想起了当初
Congratulations, Fiona.
You remind me of me.
22年前 我也是在这开始的 同一张桌子
22 years ago, I started
here, at that very desk.
♪ I come to life ♪
♪ when the night is in ♪
嗨 我是世界茶杯的Fiona
Hi, this is Fiona with worldwide cup.
今天过的如何呢
How are you today?
我很好 谢谢你 我注意到你
I'm well, thank you, we've noticed that you
有一段时间没有购买了
haven't renewed your order in a while.
♪ Going down, going down ♪
♪ yeah, I'm going down to
the devil's playground ♪
♪ hey, hey, hey, hey ♪
等待着最后的结果
Still awaiting final vote.
有15个是去年被提名的
15 of these nominees have
been pending since last year.
有18个是得到两党连立的
18 of them have received
strong bipartisan support
参议院司法委员会大力支持
from the Senate Judiciary Committee.
这些都是为美国参议院投票
These are non-controversial
nominees that are due
所确定的提名人
the up or down vote for
the United States Senate.
没有任何理由可以拖延履行
And there is no justification
for the delay of the Senate
参议院的责任
carrying out its
constitutional responsibility...
操
Fuck.
嘿
Hey.
嗨
Hi, um...
我被麻省理工录取了
I got into M.I.T.
♪ ♪
全额奖学金
It's a full ride.
话说回来 如果没有你 我不会成功的
Anyway, it wouldn't have
happened without you.
唔
So...
谢谢你
thank you.
♪ Oh, there's the river
that winds on forever ♪
♪ I'm gonna see where it leads ♪
你要去吗
Are you gonna go?
♪ Oh, there's a mountain
that no man has mounted ♪
♪ I'm gonna stand on the peak ♪
♪ out there's a land
that time don't command ♪
♪ wanna be the first to arrive ♪
♪ no time for ponderin'
why I'm a-wanderin' on ♪
♪ while we're both still alive ♪
♪ to the ends of the earth,
would you follow me? ♪
♪ ♪
♪ there's a world that was meant ♪
♪ for us to see ♪
♪ to the ends of the earth,
would you follow me? ♪
♪ ♪
♪ well, if you want, I will
say my good-byes to thee ♪
♪ ♪
[Phone rings]
我是Steve 有事请留言
It's Steve. Leave some words.
最后一次 我保证
Last message, I promise.
不管你在哪
Wherever you are...
再见
Bye.
♪ To the ends of the earth,
would you follow me? ♪
♪ ♪
♪ there's a world that
was meant for us to see ♪
♪ ♪
♪ to the ends of the earth,
would you follow me? ♪
♪ ♪
♪ well, if you want, I will
say my good-byes to thee ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I was ready to die for you, baby ♪
♪ doesn't mean I'm ready to stay ♪
♪ what good is living the
life you've been given ♪
♪ if all you do is stand in one place? ♪
♪ I'm on a river that winds on forever ♪
♪ follow till I get where I'm going ♪
♪ maybe I'm heading to die,
but I'm still gonna try ♪
♪ I guess I'm going alone ♪
♪ ♪
无耻之徒字幕组倾情奉献